http://www.bwc.com/privacy-policy

Menu
AboutCorporate InvolvementSignature ExperienceCommunity InvolvementPress ReleasesTradeshows & EventsCareersHistoryCorporate BrochureVisitors handbookCapabilitiesProductsComponents & AccessoriesDualVee® - Linear Vee Groove Guide Wheels DetailsMadeWell® – Radial Wheels & Crown Rollers DetailsLoPro® Gantry Kits DetailsGV3 Linear Guidance and Transmission DetailsSL2 Stainless Steel Slides DetailsPRT2 Precision Ring and Track DetailsHDS2 Heavy Duty Slide DetailsHDRT Heavy Duty Ring and Track DetailsMCS Aluminum Machine Frame DetailsManual Linear Guide SystemsDualVee® – Linear Vee Groove Guide Wheels DetailsMinVee® Miniature Linear Slide DetailsSimpleSelect® Linear Guides DetailsUtiliTrak® Compact Linear Guide DetailsGV3 Linear Guidance and Transmission DetailsHDS2 Heavy Duty Slide DetailsHTS Telescopic Ball Slides DetailsPRT2 Precision Ring and Track DetailsSL2 Stainless Steel Slides DetailsSteadyRail™ Linear Stages DetailsMHD Heavy Duty Track Guides DetailsActuated Linear Guide SystemsLoPro® Linear Actuators DetailsDLS Driven Linear System DetailsHDCS Heavy Duty Compact Screw DetailsHDLS Heavy Duty Linear System DetailsMHD Heavy Duty Track Guides DetailsPDU2 Profile Driven Unit Actuator DetailsDAPDU2 Double Acting Profile Driven Unit DetailsPSD Precison Screw Drive Actuator DetailsSBD Sealed Belt Driven Actuator DetailsXLA™ Linear Actuators DetailsECO60™ Linear Actuators DetailsSlickStick™ Linear Actuators DetailsSteadyRail™ Linear Stages DetailsRotary Guide SystemsGFX Guidance System Details1-Trak Single Piece Track System DetailsALR Aluminum Rings DetailsDTS Driven Track System DetailsHDRT Heavy Duty Ring and Track DetailsPRT2 Precision Ring and Track DetailsCustom SolutionsExtruded Profile Guides DetailsSpecialty Bearings DetailsBuy NowProduct SelectorResource CenterProduct
ConfiguratorApplication StoriesCatalogsFAQProduct Lead TimeWhite PapersProduct Status NotificationVideosTechnical DataCAD FilesUser ManualsCertificationsITARRoHS CompliantBay Area Green BusinessAS9100D and ISO 9001 Certified Quality ManagementSystemWBENC / Certified Woman-Ownedsupplier DiversitYContact
Request quote
reach via chat
general inquiries
call
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature'
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information)
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Creating an account has many benefits:
Please login to use the Configurator and provide the login form. or please sign up for an account to use the Configurator.
Email
Password
Sign In
Forgot Your Password?
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Subscribe
© 2020 - Bishop-Wisecarver
